http://www.chicagoautoshow.com/privacy-policy/

Advertisement
Acceptance of Terms - By using this Web Site, users assent to this privacy policy. If users do not agree to this privacy policy, users must not use this or any of ChicagoAutoShow.com's Web sites. ChicagoAutoShow.com reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this privacy policy at any time, so users are encouraged to review this policy from time to time. Users' continued use of this Web Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean users' acceptance of those changes. Users of ChicagoAutoShow.com, the official Chicago Auto Show app and patrons of the Chicago Auto Show also accept the privacy policy as stated here.
It is the policy of ChicagoAutoShow.com to respect and protect the privacy of its users and recognize the importance of protecting the personal information it collects about its users. ChicagoAutoShow.com would like to assure its users that this privacy policy meets the requirements of the various privacy laws and regulations, including, without limitation, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998.
Your User Information - All personal information collected at www.chicagoautoshow.com (the "Web Site") by ChicagoAutoShow.com and/or its parents, affiliates, subsidiaries, affiliated companies and/or promotional partners or agencies will be utilized primarily for internal purposes with the goal of enhancing the user's online experience.
ChicagoAutoShow.com collects information in several ways including, without limitation, primarily the following:
Some personal information is gathered when you register to participate in or receive information via electronic mail or otherwise about: automobiles in general, your automobile, automobile insurance, general and personal automobile maintenance, general and personal finance, general and personal credit, automobile dealerships, quotes, research, statistics, advice, Web sites, games, contests, sweepstakes, promotional events and/or any other event that takes place on the Web Site. During such registration, ChicagoAutoShow.com may ask for information such as, without limitation, a user's name, electronic mail address, birth date, gender, zip code and country, and other optional information that may be particular to that registration process;
ChicagoAutoShow.com collects information on its users' demographics, interests and behavior based on the information provided to ChicagoAutoShow.com from the registration described in (1) above, from ChicagoAutoShow.com's server log files, from surveys, from cookies (see below) and from IP addresses (see below). ChicagoAutoShow.com does this to better understand and serve its users. This collected information/research is generally compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis;
For reasons such as improving personalization of ChicagoAutoShow.com's service, ChicagoAutoShow.com might collect information about its users from other sources and add it to ChicagoAutoShow.com's account information; and
ChicagoAutoShow.com also sometimes collects updated delivery and address information from its shippers or other sources so that ChicagoAutoShow.com can correct its records and deliver or communicate more easily.
ChicagoAutoShow.com uses and/or discloses collected information in several ways, including, without limitation, primarily the following:
ChicagoAutoShow.com may use electronic mail addresses or other personally identifiable information to contact users who directly communicate with ChicagoAutoShow.com, to, among other things, fulfill prizes, track/verify compliance with ChicagoAutoShow.com policies as well as federal, state, local and other laws, and/or to solicit editorial comments and feedback. For example, ChicagoAutoShow.com may use such information to notify users that they have won a game, contest or sweepstakes or to provide a requested electronic mail newsletter or provide other requested information;
ChicagoAutoShow.com may match aggregated user information with third party data in order to better serve the interests of its users;
ChicagoAutoShow.com may disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe ChicagoAutoShow.com's services to prospective partners, advertisers and third parties and for other lawful purposes, in order to, among other things, make better alliances and provide a better user experience on the Web Site;
ChicagoAutoShow.com may use a user's personally identifiable information for editorial purposes. For example, ChicagoAutoShow.com may use information provided by a user to ChicagoAutoShow.com as part of an online survey conducted by ChicagoAutoShow.com;
Unless a user tells ChicagoAutoShow.com that he/she would prefer not to receive electronic mail from ChicagoAutoShow.com, ChicagoAutoShow.com may use collected personal information to send you electronic mail about ChicagoAutoShow.com's and/or other companies' products, promotions or services. A user may choose not to provide certain information, but then that user might not be able to take advantage of many of ChicagoAutoShow.com's features;
In some instances, collected personal information may also be used by ChicagoAutoShow.com for additional marketing and promotional purposes relating to the Web Site or other properties;
ChicagoAutoShow.com may use cookies and IP addresses as set forth in more detail below; and
ChicagoAutoShow.com may disclose user information to third parties when ChicagoAutoShow.com has reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) ChicagoAutoShow.com's rights or property, other Web Site users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. ChicagoAutoShow.com may disclose user information when ChicagoAutoShow.com believes in good faith that the law requires it.
ChicagoAutoShow.com may use agents to carry out its activities:
ChicagoAutoShow.com may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on its behalf. Examples include, without limitation, fulfilling orders, sending postal mail and electronic mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, delivering packages and providing customer service. They may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
Other than as set forth above, it is ChicagoAutoShow.com's current policy not to share any personally identifiable information provided by users with other third parties, unless specified at the time of collection or with the user's consent.
Opting Out - In the event that a user changes his or her mind and no longer wishes to share his or her personal information with ChicagoAutoShow.com, or if some personal information changes, ChicagoAutoShow.com will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update, or remove the personal data provided to ChicagoAutoShow.com. For instance, ChicagoAutoShow.com provides users with the option to unsubscribe from future email newsletters.
ChicagoAutoShow.com bears no responsibility for any action or policies of any third parties who collect any information users may disclose on the bulletin boards, chat areas or other public forums on this Web Site.
To opt out or to change your status on this Web Site contact ChicagoAutoShow.com by either electronic mail at info@cata.info or via the following number: 1-630-495-2282.
Links - Users should be aware that when they are on any portion of the Web Site, they could be directed to other Web sites and/or Online materials that are beyond ChicagoAutoShow.com's control. There are links to other Web sites from this Web Site that take users outside ChicagoAutoShow.com's service. For example, if users "click" on a banner advertisement, the "click" takes users off the Web Site. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors, and partners that may include ChicagoAutoShow.com's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other Web sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information and have their own privacy policies. To ensure the protection of its users' privacy while on the Web Site, ChicagoAutoShow.com will make an effort to provide a notice and a link to this privacy policy on all pages where personally identifying information is collected.
Users should keep in mind that whenever they give out personal information Online - for example, via message boards or chat rooms - that information could be collected and used by people that users do not know. While ChicagoAutoShow.com strives to protect users' personal information and privacy, ChicagoAutoShow.com cannot guarantee the security of any information users disclose Online, and users do so at their own risk.
ChicagoAutoShow.com's policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet or any Online technology, and therefore beyond ChicagoAutoShow.com's control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation.
ChicagoAutoShow.com DOES NOT KNOWINGLY COLLECT INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN THIRTEEN (13) YEARS OF AGE OR YOUNGER.
ChicagoAutoShow.com does not knowingly collect information from children thirteen (13) years of age or younger. If you are under thirteen (13), do not send any information about yourself to ChicagoAutoShow.com, including, information like your name, address and/or electronic mail address. ChicagoAutoShow.com encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to supervise their children's activities on ChicagoAutoShow.com's sites. ChicagoAutoShow.com alerts parents that this Web Site features content exploring mature themes not appropriate for children. This Web Site is not a Web site directed to children under the age of 13. ChicagoAutoShow.com suggests that parents consider using parental control tools available from Online services and software manufacturers that may help ensure a child friendly Online environment and help direct their children to suitable, child-oriented Web sites. Further, ChicagoAutoShow.com request that all users to the Web Site that are under the age of 13 not disclose or provide any personal information on this Web Site. In the event that ChicagoAutoShow.com discovers that a child under the age of 13 has provided ChicagoAutoShow.com with his or her personal information, ChicagoAutoShow.com will immediately delete the child's personal information from its system.
Because ChicagoAutoShow.com does not knowingly collect such information, ChicagoAutoShow.com does not knowingly provide any personally identifying information from its users under 13 years of age, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever. ChicagoAutoShow.com also does not knowingly allow users under 13 years of age to be listed in any member directory or to receive direct marketing communications from ChicagoAutoShow.com or to be sent third-party offers.
Use of Cookies - Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for the user by saving the user's preferences while the user is at the Web Site. ChicagoAutoShow.com never saves passwords or credit card information in cookies.
By showing how and when users use a Web site, cookies help ChicagoAutoShow.com see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to this Web Site are based on such data as total number of users and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. ChicagoAutoShow.com uses the information from cookies to provide services better tailored to this Web Site's users.
Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent.
Use of IP Addresses - An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers - the big computers that "serve up" Web pages - automatically identify your computer by its IP address.
ChicagoAutoShow.com may collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our site. When users request pages from this Web Site, our servers log the users' IP addresses. ChicagoAutoShow.com does not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a user's session will be logged but the user remains anonymous to us. ChicagoAutoShow.com can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when ChicagoAutoShow.com feels it is necessary to enforce compliance with our house rules, terms of service, any law or regulation or to protect our service, Web Site, customers, or others.
Some services within the Web Site, such as certain message boards, may display IP addresses along with the message poster's name and message. Please review each service prior to use and only use those that disclose information you are comfortable with sharing.
Security - The importance of privacy and security for all personally identifiable information associated with users is of utmost concern to ChicagoAutoShow.com. ChicagoAutoShow.com exercises great care in providing secure transmission of users' information from the users' personal computer to ChicagoAutoShow.com's servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while ChicagoAutoShow.com strives to protect users personal information, ChicagoAutoShow.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information users transmit to ChicagoAutoShow.com or from ChicagoAutoShow.com's Online products or services, and users do so at their own risk. Once ChicagoAutoShow.com receives users' transmission, ChicagoAutoShow.com makes its best effort to ensure the transmission's security on ChicagoAutoShow.com's systems. If credit card information is transmitted, ChicagoAutoShow.com uses industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption.
Advertisement
close (X)
